[
    {
        "question": "Where do you go to buy zombies?",
        "answer": "The monSTORE!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the man say to his forgetful zombie wife?",
        "answer": "You forgot your HEAD because it wasn&apos;t attached!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did the zombie take out for dinner?",
        "answer": "His GHOULfriend!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie ignore all his new Facebook friends?",
        "answer": "He was still DIGESTING all his old Facebook friends!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie&apos;s favorite toy?",
        "answer": "A DEADY bear!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did everyone say about the big zombie party?",
        "answer": "It was DEAD &amp; full of STIFFS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say to his date?",
        "answer": "I just love a woman with BRAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the zombie&apos;s greatest invention?",
        "answer": "Canned BRAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between zombies &amp; patched jeans?",
        "answer": "Zombies are DEAD men, jeans are menDEAD!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do all the Apple zombies keep telling Steve Jobs?",
        "answer": "We&apos;re DYING to have YOU for dinner!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the zombie&apos;s &quot;Grease&quot; audition go?",
        "answer": "Bad, they couldn&apos;t envision Danny as GREEN, ROTTING &amp; GRUESOME!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie hope for before his blind date?",
        "answer": "Someone with a PULSE &amp; plenty of BRAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie call his new dating handbook?",
        "answer": "&quot;DYING To Meet You!&quot;"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why didn&apos;t the zombie get the job?",
        "answer": "They wanted someone with more energy &amp; less ROTTING flesh!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the zombie treat every day of death?",
        "answer": "Like he was LIVING!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie buy a Jet Ski?",
        "answer": "He wanted to ENJOY the apocalypse!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a zombie with lots of kids?",
        "answer": "A MOMster!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of candy do zombies refuse to eat?",
        "answer": "LIFE Savers!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie&apos;s friend say after she joined Greenpeace?",
        "answer": "Uggghhh, you&apos;re one of those annoying GREEN zombies!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a zombie door-to-door salesman?",
        "answer": "A DEAD ringer!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do zombies go swimming?",
        "answer": "The DEAD Sea!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do most zombies live?",
        "answer": "On DEAD end streets!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the safest place in your home from a zombie?",
        "answer": "The LIVING room!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the zombie war?",
        "answer": "Nobody, it was a DEAD tie!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie&apos;s ex say when she wouldn&apos;t stop calling?",
        "answer": "You&apos;re DEAD to me!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call a dead bee?",
        "answer": "A zomBEE!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do zombies eat dinner with their family?",
        "answer": "No, their family IS the dinner!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say before his fight?",
        "answer": "Do you want a PIECE of me?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do dark circles around the zombie&apos;s eyes make him look dead?",
        "answer": "No, but being DEAD does!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie go crazy?",
        "answer": "He had LOST his mind!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie&apos;s favorite meal?",
        "answer": "A MANwich!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say after seeing his neighbor&apos;s new car?",
        "answer": "I&apos;m GREEN with envy!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie say to his wife Barbara?",
        "answer": "I&apos;m coming to get you, BARBARA!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are zombies like computers?",
        "answer": "They use megaBITES!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you know a zombie is tired?",
        "answer": "He&apos;s DEAD on his feet!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie do after he dumped his girlfriend?",
        "answer": "He wiped his BUTT!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie&apos;s favorite shampoo?",
        "answer": "Head &amp; Shoulders!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of streets do zombies like best?",
        "answer": "DEAD end!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does a zombie get when he comes home late for dinner?",
        "answer": "The cold SHOULDER!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie eat after his teeth were pulled?",
        "answer": "The DENTIST!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do zombies go on cruises?",
        "answer": "The DEADiterranean Sea!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do zombies wear when it&apos;s raining?",
        "answer": "BRAAAINcoats!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do zombies eat candy with their fingers?",
        "answer": "No, they EAT the FINGERS separately!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie cross the road?",
        "answer": "To get to the BRAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Knock...knock! Who&apos;s there? Zombie! Zombie who?",
        "answer": "BRAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do they smooth the ice on a zombie hockey rink?",
        "answer": "With a ZomBONI!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does it take to become a zombie?",
        "answer": "DEADication!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do zombies order at bars?",
        "answer": "A shot of To-KILL-Ya!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you hear about the zombie who tortured his victims with music?",
        "answer": "His BACH was worse than his bite!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What time do zombies wake up?",
        "answer": "At ATE o&apos;clock!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie&apos;s favorite TV show?",
        "answer": "&quot;CHOMPING On The Stars!&quot;"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do zombies serve their country?",
        "answer": "In the Marine CORPSE!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What cereal does a zombie eat for breakfast?",
        "answer": "Raisin BRAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do zombies eat popcorn with their fingers?",
        "answer": "No, they EAT the FINGERS separately!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why do zombies make good DJs?",
        "answer": "They produce lots of sound BITES!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie go to the hospital?",
        "answer": "He wanted to learn some SICK jokes!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie lose his lawsuit?",
        "answer": "He had NO LEG to STAND ON!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you do if you see a zombie?",
        "answer": "Hope it&apos;s HALLOWEEN!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did one zombie say to the other zombie while eating a comedian?",
        "answer": "This tastes FUNNY!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do vegetarian zombies crave?",
        "answer": "GRAAAINS...more GRAAAAAAINS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do little zombies play?",
        "answer": "CORPSES &amp; Robbers!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the zombie&apos;s friend say when introduced to his new girlfriend?",
        "answer": "Where the heck did you DIG her UP from?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who do cowboy zombies fight?",
        "answer": "DEADskins!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What has a dog&apos;s head, a cat&apos;s tail &amp; brains all over its face?",
        "answer": "A zombie LEAVING the PET STORE!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is black, white &amp; dead all over?",
        "answer": "A zombie in a TUXEDO!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie cross the road?",
        "answer": "He wanted to EAT the chicken!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you hear about the zombie who was expelled from school?",
        "answer": "He kept BUTTERING up his teacher!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie stop teaching?",
        "answer": "He only had one PUPIL!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do zombies tell their future?",
        "answer": "With their HORRORscope!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do zombies like to eat at cookouts?",
        "answer": "Beanie HALLOWEENies!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie go to the orthodontist?",
        "answer": "To improve his BITE!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many zombies does it take to screw in a light bulb?",
        "answer": "None, zombies CAN&apos;T FIT in a light bulb &amp; they DON&apos;T screw!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the zombie put poison in people&apos;s corn flakes?",
        "answer": "He was a CEREAL killer!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you get when you cross a zombie with a snowman?",
        "answer": "FrostBITE!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie&apos;s favorite mode of transportation?",
        "answer": "SCAREplanes!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of dogs do zombies like best?",
        "answer": "BLOODhound!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the dyslexic zombie starve to death?",
        "answer": "He couldn&apos;t find any SNIAAARB!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was the zombie afraid to cross the road?",
        "answer": "He had LOST his GUTS!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a zombie&apos;s favorite football team?",
        "answer": "The Washington DEADskins!"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do zombies keep their hair in place?",
        "answer": "With SCARE spray!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is black, white &amp; red all over?",
        "answer": "A nun being EATEN by zombies!"
    }
]